<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cornstarch on Huny-B.info</title>
    <link>https://Huny-B.info/ingredients/cornstarch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cornstarch on Huny-B.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2018 Huny-B CBD-Oil Ltd Co. All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://Huny-B.info/ingredients/cornstarch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>100 mg CBD Serenity Bath Salts Sweet Orange &amp; Rosemary</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024226/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024226/</guid>
      <description>100 mg CBD Serenity Bath Salts Sweet Orange &amp;amp; Rosemary Front Panel Huny-B CBD 100 mg CBD Serenity Bath Salts Sweet Orange &amp;amp; Ginger Net Wt. 8 oz. 1 application  Information Panels Intended Use
Designed to re-energize and invigorate by taking advantage of the wonderful energizing and uplifting properties of CBD, Sweet Orange and Ginger Essential Oils
Direction for Safe Use Sprinkle 1&amp;frasl;4 cup or more Serenity Baths Salts into a warm bath and enjoy the soak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melts Lavender &amp; Bergamot</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024141/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024141/</guid>
      <description>20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melts Lavender &amp;amp; Bergamot Front Panel Huny-B CBD 20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melt Lavender &amp;amp; Bergamot Net Wt. 2 oz. 1 application  Information Panels Intended Use
Designed to soothe your relax your mind and body with the healing properties of CBD, Lavender and Bergamot Essential Oils by the way of aromatherapy and entering your pores through the steam.
Direction for Safe Use</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melts Peppermint &amp; Eucalyptus</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024134/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024134/</guid>
      <description>20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melts Peppermint &amp;amp; Eucalyptus Front Panel
Huny-B CBD 20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melt Pepperment &amp;amp; Eucalyptus Net Wt. 2 oz. 1 application  Information Panels Intended Use
Designed to soothe your sore muscles with the healing properties of CBD, Peppermint and Eucalyptus Essential Oils by the way of aromatherapy and entering your pours through the steam.
Direction for Safe Use
Place your Serenity Shower Steamer in the back of the shower away from the direct spray and enjoy the aromatherapy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melts Sweet Orange &amp; Ginger</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024127/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024127/</guid>
      <description>20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melts Sweet Orange &amp;amp; Ginger Front Panel Huny-B CBD 20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melt Sweet Orange &amp;amp; Ginger Net Wt. 2 oz. 1 application  Information Panels Intended Use
Designed to uplift and energize your mind and body with the healing properties of CBD, Sweet Orange and Ginger Essential Oils by the way of aromatherapy and entering your pores through the steam.
Direction for Safe Use</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>50 mg CBD Serenity Bath Bombs Lavender &amp; Rosemary</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024028/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024028/</guid>
      <description>Our Serenity Bath Bombs have 50 mg’s of CBD and are the bomb above all of Bath Bombs. With the combination of CBD and Essential Oils these Bath Bombs will give you a wonderful soaking experience! Enjoy the &amp;ldquo;Spa like&amp;rdquo; experience from you own home!
Front Panel Huny-B CBD 50 mg CBD Serenity Bath Bomb Lavender &amp;amp; Rosemary Net Wt. 6 oz. 1 application  Information Panels Intended Use</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>50 mg CBD Serenity Bath Bombs Peppermint &amp; Eucalyptus</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024011/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024011/</guid>
      <description>50 mg CBD Serenity Bath Bombs Peppermint &amp;amp; Eucalyptus Our Serenity Bath Bombs have 50 mg’s of CBD and are the bomb above all of Bath Bombs. With the combination of CBD and Essential Oils these Bath Bombs will give you a wonderful soaking experience! Enjoy the &amp;ldquo;Spa like&amp;rdquo; experience from you own home!
Front Panel&amp;rdquo; Huny-B CBD 50 mg CBD Serenity Bath Bomb Pepperment &amp;amp; Eucalyptus Net Wt. 6 oz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>50 mg CBD Serenity Bath Bombs Sweet Orange &amp; Ginger</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024035/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024035/</guid>
      <description>50 mg CBD Serenity Bath Bombs Sweet Orange &amp;amp; Ginger Our Serenity Bath Bombs have 50 mg’s of CBD and are the bomb above all of Bath Bombs. With the combination of CBD and Essential Oils these Bath Bombs will give you a wonderful soaking experience! Enjoy the &amp;ldquo;Spa like&amp;rdquo; experience from you own home!
Front Panel Huny-B CBD 50 mg CBD Serenity Bath Bomb Sweet Orange &amp;amp; Ginger Net Wt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>50 mg CBD Serenity Bath Bombs Pepperment &amp; Eucalyptus 1 app</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/c/01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 14:23:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/c/01/</guid>
      <description>We designed our 50 mg CBD Peppermint and Euclyptus Bath Bombs to soothe your sore muscles by taking advantage of the healing properties of CBD, Peppermint and Eucalyptus Essential Oils. Educate Yourself. Learn more now about research regarding active ingredients. Buy now for $12.99 USD.
Net Wt. 6 oz.
1 application
Information Panels Direction for Safe Use Drop your bathbomb into a warm bath and enjoy the soak.
Warnings Caution: Tub may be slippery when entering and exiting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>