<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hemp Oil Liniments on Huny-B.info</title>
    <link>https://Huny-B.info/products/hemp-oil-liniments/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hemp Oil Liniments on Huny-B.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2018 Huny-B CBD-Oil Ltd Co. All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://Huny-B.info/products/hemp-oil-liniments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>250 mg CBD Hemp Oil Heat Salve Liniment</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024318/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024318/</guid>
      <description>250 mg CBD Hemp Oil Heat Salve Liniment For those who prefer mild stimulation and heat we have created the Huny-B CBD salve. As you can see the ingredients ranging from the obvious CBD and Hemp Seed Oil; to soothing Arnica. Chamomile and Eucalyptus provides a stark contrast with the Essential Oils such as Black Pepper oil, Cinnamon oil, Camphor oil , and Menthol Crystals . Of course there are many more essential oils and ingredients besides these, but the point is that this creates a unique feeling that is just as welcome on sore muscles, aches and pains as it is on healthy skin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>250 mg CBD Hemp Oil Liniment Bar</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024400/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024400/</guid>
      <description>250 mg CBD Hemp Oil Liniment Ba Front Panel Huny-B CBD Hemp Oil Liniment Hemp Oil Heat Liniment Bar Net Wt. 2.0 oz.  Information Panels Intended Use
We have designed our signature Hemp Oil Liniment Bar to penetrate sore muscles and joints by using and aging CBD, derived from the Hemp Plant, Hemp Seed Oil, Arnica, and 20 Essential Oils and Herbs in a certain blend to get the job done!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>500 mg CBD Hemp Oil Liniment Bar</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024424/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024424/</guid>
      <description>500 mg CBD Hemp Oil Liniment Bar ##Front Panel
Huny-B CBD Hemp Oil Liniment 500 mg Hemp Oil Heat Liniment Bar Net Wt. 2.0 oz.  Information Panels Intended Use
We have designed our signature Hemp Oil Liniment Bar to penetrate sore muscles and joints by using and aging CBD, derived from the Hemp Plant, Hemp Seed Oil, Arnica, and 20 Essential Oils and Herbs in a certain blend to get the job done!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>