<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Serenity Shower Steamers on Huny-B.info</title>
    <link>https://Huny-B.info/products/serenity-shower-steamers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Serenity Shower Steamers on Huny-B.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2018 Huny-B CBD-Oil Ltd Co. All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://Huny-B.info/products/serenity-shower-steamers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melts Lavender &amp; Bergamot</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024141/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024141/</guid>
      <description>20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melts Lavender &amp;amp; Bergamot Front Panel Huny-B CBD 20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melt Lavender &amp;amp; Bergamot Net Wt. 2 oz. 1 application  Information Panels Intended Use
Designed to soothe your relax your mind and body with the healing properties of CBD, Lavender and Bergamot Essential Oils by the way of aromatherapy and entering your pores through the steam.
Direction for Safe Use</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melts Peppermint &amp; Eucalyptus</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024134/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024134/</guid>
      <description>20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melts Peppermint &amp;amp; Eucalyptus Front Panel
Huny-B CBD 20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melt Pepperment &amp;amp; Eucalyptus Net Wt. 2 oz. 1 application  Information Panels Intended Use
Designed to soothe your sore muscles with the healing properties of CBD, Peppermint and Eucalyptus Essential Oils by the way of aromatherapy and entering your pours through the steam.
Direction for Safe Use
Place your Serenity Shower Steamer in the back of the shower away from the direct spray and enjoy the aromatherapy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melts Sweet Orange &amp; Ginger</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024127/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024127/</guid>
      <description>20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melts Sweet Orange &amp;amp; Ginger Front Panel Huny-B CBD 20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melt Sweet Orange &amp;amp; Ginger Net Wt. 2 oz. 1 application  Information Panels Intended Use
Designed to uplift and energize your mind and body with the healing properties of CBD, Sweet Orange and Ginger Essential Oils by the way of aromatherapy and entering your pores through the steam.
Direction for Safe Use</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>