<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lavender Essential Oil on Huny-B.info</title>
    <link>https://Huny-B.info/ingredients/lavender-essential-oil/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lavender Essential Oil on Huny-B.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2018 Huny-B CBD-Oil Ltd Co. All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://Huny-B.info/ingredients/lavender-essential-oil/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>100 mg CBD Serenity Bath Salts Lavender &amp; YlangYlang</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024219/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024219/</guid>
      <description>100 mg CBD Serenity Bath Salts Lavender &amp;amp; YlangYlang Front Panel Huny-B CBD 100 mg CBD Serenity Bath Salts Lavender &amp;amp; YlangYlang Net Wt. 8 oz. 1 application  Information Panels Intended Use
Designed to calm and relax your body and mind by taking advantage of the tranquil properties of CBD, Lavender and YlangYlang Essential Oils.
Direction for Safe Use
Sprinkle 1&amp;frasl;4 cup or more Serenity Baths Salts into a warm bath and enjoy the soak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1000 CBD Serenity Hemp &amp; Huny Body Butter Lavender and YlangYlang</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024653/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024653/</guid>
      <description>1000 CBD Serenity Hemp &amp;amp; Huny Body Butter Lavender and YlangYlang Our luxurious 1000 mg Hemp &amp;amp; Huny Body Butters lets you indulge in an intensive, creamy all over body moisturizer. Its rich thick, buttery formula melts into your skin and absorbs easily without feeling greasy. Leaves the skin feeling softer and smoother to the touch, with a wonderful delicate scent. Infused with CBD, Hemp Seed Oil, and Essential Oils our Body Butter is designed to penetrate your muscles to help with: Dry Skin, Itching, Muscle Pain, Muscle Soreness, Muscle Spasms, Joint Pain, Nerve Pain, and Inflammation plus so much more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1000 CBD Serenity Hemp &amp; Huny Lotion Lavender and YlangYlang</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024592/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024592/</guid>
      <description>1000 CBD Serenity Hemp &amp;amp; Huny Lotion Lavender and YlangYlang Huny-B&amp;rsquo;s 1000 mg Hemp and Huny Lotion is enriched with CBD derived from the Hemp Plant and 100% Pure Hemp Seed Oil and blended with natural extracts to provide dramatic skin hydration and nourishment to help improve the health and condition of skin. Hemp Seed Oil is one of nature&amp;rsquo;s richest sources of Essential Fatty Acids and Key Amino Acids containing natural proteins, vitamins, antioxidants, and minerals, vital for healthy skin conditioning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melts Lavender &amp; Bergamot</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024141/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024141/</guid>
      <description>20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melts Lavender &amp;amp; Bergamot Front Panel Huny-B CBD 20 mg CBD Serenity Shower Melt Lavender &amp;amp; Bergamot Net Wt. 2 oz. 1 application  Information Panels Intended Use
Designed to soothe your relax your mind and body with the healing properties of CBD, Lavender and Bergamot Essential Oils by the way of aromatherapy and entering your pores through the steam.
Direction for Safe Use</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>200 mg CBD Serenity Hemp &amp; Huny Lotion Lavender and YlangYlang</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024516/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024516/</guid>
      <description>200 mg CBD Serenity Hemp &amp;amp; Huny Lotion Lavender and YlangYlang Huny-B&amp;rsquo;s 200 mg Hemp and Huny Lotion is enriched with CBD derived from the Hemp Plant and 100% Pure Hemp Seed Oil and blended with natural extracts to provide dramatic skin hydration and nourishment to help improve the health and condition of skin. Hemp Seed Oil is one of nature&amp;rsquo;s richest sources of Essential Fatty Acids and Key Amino Acids containing natural proteins, vitamins, antioxidants, and minerals, vital for healthy skin conditioning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>50 mg CBD Serenity Bath Bombs Lavender &amp; Rosemary</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024028/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024028/</guid>
      <description>Our Serenity Bath Bombs have 50 mg’s of CBD and are the bomb above all of Bath Bombs. With the combination of CBD and Essential Oils these Bath Bombs will give you a wonderful soaking experience! Enjoy the &amp;ldquo;Spa like&amp;rdquo; experience from you own home!
Front Panel Huny-B CBD 50 mg CBD Serenity Bath Bomb Lavender &amp;amp; Rosemary Net Wt. 6 oz. 1 application  Information Panels Intended Use</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>500 CBD Serenity Hemp &amp; Huny Body Butter Lavender and YlangYlang</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024615/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024615/</guid>
      <description>500 CBD Serenity Hemp &amp;amp; Huny Body Butter Lavender and YlangYlang Our luxurious 500 mg Hemp &amp;amp; Huny Body Butters lets you indulge in an intensive, creamy all over body moisturizer. Its rich thick, buttery formula melts into your skin and absorbs easily without feeling greasy. Leaves the skin feeling softer and smoother to the touch, with a wonderful delicate scent. Infused with CBD, Hemp Seed Oil, and Essential Oils our Body Butter is designed to penetrate your muscles to help with: Dry Skin, Itching, Muscle Pain, Muscle Soreness, Muscle Spasms, Joint Pain, Nerve Pain, and Inflammation plus so much more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>500 CBD Serenity Hemp &amp; Huny Lotion Lavender and YlangYlang</title>
      <link>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024554/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:11:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Huny-B.info/post/850003024554/</guid>
      <description>500 CBD Serenity Hemp &amp;amp; Huny Lotion Lavender and YlangYlang Huny-B&amp;rsquo;s 500 mg Hemp and Huny Lotion is enriched with CBD derived from the Hemp Plant and 100% Pure Hemp Seed Oil and blended with natural extracts to provide dramatic skin hydration and nourishment to help improve the health and condition of skin. Hemp Seed Oil is one of nature&amp;rsquo;s richest sources of Essential Fatty Acids and Key Amino Acids containing natural proteins, vitamins, antioxidants, and minerals, vital for healthy skin conditioning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>